import { Exercise } from ".";

export const NUMBERS: Exercise[] = [
  {
    "question": "–Ω–æ–ª—å",
    "answer": "no≈Ç¬¥",
    "extra": "0Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "–æ–¥–∏–Ω",
    "answer": "odin",
    "extra": "1Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "–¥–≤–∞",
    "answer": "dwa",
    "extra": "2Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "—Ç—Ä–∏",
    "answer": "tri",
    "extra": "3Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "—á–µ—Ç—ã—Ä–µ",
    "answer": "czietyrie",
    "extra": "4Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "–ø—è—Ç—å",
    "answer": "piat¬¥",
    "extra": "5Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "—à–µ—Å—Ç—å",
    "answer": "szest¬¥",
    "extra": "6Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "—Å–µ–º—å",
    "answer": "siem¬¥",
    "extra": "7Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "–≤–æ—Å–µ–º—å",
    "answer": "wosiem¬¥",
    "extra": "8Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "–¥–µ–≤—è—Ç—å",
    "answer": "diewiat¬¥",
    "extra": "9Ô∏è‚É£"
  },
  {
    "question": "–¥–µ—Å—è—Ç—å",
    "answer": "diesiat¬¥",
    "extra": "üîü"
  },
  {
    "question": "–æ–¥–∏–Ω–Ω–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "odinnadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "11"
  },
  {
    "question": "–¥–≤–µ–Ω–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "dwinadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "12"
  },
  {
    "question": "—Ç—Ä–∏–Ω–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "trinadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "13"
  },
  {
    "question": "—á–µ—Ç—ã—Ä–Ω–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "czietyrnadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "14"
  },
  {
    "question": "–ø—è—Ç–Ω–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "piatnadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "15"
  },
  {
    "question": "—à–µ—Å—Ç–Ω–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "szestnadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "16"
  },
  {
    "question": "—Å–µ–º–Ω–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "siemnadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "17"
  },
  {
    "question": "–≤–æ—Å–µ–º–Ω–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "wosiemnadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "18"
  },
  {
    "question": "–¥–µ–≤—è—Ç–Ω–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "diewiatnadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "19"
  },
  {
    "question": "–¥–≤–∞–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "dwadcat¬¥",
    "extra": "20"
  },
  {
    "question": "—Ç—Ä–∏–¥—Ü–∞—Ç—å",
    "answer": "tridcat¬¥",
    "extra": "30"
  },
  {
    "question": "—Å–æ—Ä–æ–∫",
    "answer": "sorok",
    "extra": "40"
  },
  {
    "question": "–ø—è—Ç—å–¥–µ—Å—è—Ç",
    "answer": "piat¬¥diesiat",
    "extra": "50"
  },
  {
    "question": "—à–µ—Å—Ç—å–¥–µ—Å—è—Ç",
    "answer": "szest¬¥diesiat",
    "extra": "60"
  },
  {
    "question": "—Å–µ–º—å–¥–µ—Å—è—Ç",
    "answer": "siem¬¥diesiat",
    "extra": "70"
  },
  {
    "question": "–≤–æ—Å–µ–º—å–¥–µ—Å—è—Ç",
    "answer": "wosiem¬¥diesiat",
    "extra": "80"
  },
  {
    "question": "–¥–µ–≤—è–Ω–æ—Å—Ç–æ",
    "answer": "diewianosto",
    "extra": "90"
  },
  {
    "question": "—Å—Ç–æ",
    "answer": "sto",
    "extra": "100"
  }
];
